http://www.nissan.co.uk/legal/cookies.html

Skip to main content
{"e-nv200-combi":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"27250"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"ENV200ME0B","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"5450"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"29755"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"32700"}},"nv250":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"17090"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"NV250X61N","OTR":{"modelPrice":"17090"}},"juke-test-retail":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"JUKEF15H","OTR":{"modelPrice":"15520"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"14935"}},"nv250-cs":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"17090"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"NV250X61N","OTR":{"modelPrice":"17090"}},"micra-my18-verstion-tray":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"MICRAK14B","OTR":{"modelPrice":"12880"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"12655"}},"leaf-my19":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"LEAFZE1A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26845"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"29790"}},"new-x-trail-cs":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"XTRAILT32D","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26835"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"25910"}},"juke-my19-retail":{"Updated_On":"2020.12.01.10.05.50","modelCode":"JUKEF16A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"18360"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"18090"}},"leaf-my20":{"Updated_On":"2020.11.20.10.01.39","modelCode":"LEAFZE1A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26845"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"29790"}},"juke-cs":{"Updated_On":"2020.12.01.10.05.50","modelCode":"JUKEF16A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"18360"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"18090"}},"micra-cs":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"MICRAK14C","OTR":{"modelPrice":"14500"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"13985"}},"x-trail-my18":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.08","modelCode":"XTRAILT32J","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26835"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"25910"}},"e-nv200":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"26250"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"ENV200ME0A","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"5250"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"20005"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"31500"}},"navara-cs":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"20500"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"NAVARAD23B","OTR":{"modelPrice":"24915"}},"370z-my20":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"23170.83"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.08","modelCode":"370ZZ34L","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"4634.17"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"30035"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"27805"}},"nv400-cs":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"26390"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"NV400X62B","OTR":{"modelPrice":"24705"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"29583"}},"nv400":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"26390"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"NV400X62B","OTR":{"modelPrice":"24705"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"29583"}},"x-trail-my18-old":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.08","modelCode":"XTRAILT32D","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26835"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"25910"}},"nv300":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"23390"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"NV300X82A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"21670"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"25638"}},"micra-my19":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"MICRAK14C","OTR":{"modelPrice":"14500"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"13985"}},"nv300-cs":{"default":{"modelPrice":"21655"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"NV300X82A"},"new-leaf-cs":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"LEAFZE1A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26690"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"30135"}},"e-nv200-cs":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"26250"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"ENV200ME0A","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"5250"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"20005"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"31500"}},"qashqai-my19":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"19062.5"},"Updated_On":"2020.11.20.10.01.39","modelCode":"QASHQAIJ11B","OTR":{"modelPrice":"23550"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"22875"}},"gt-r-my21":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"69887.5"},"Updated_On":"2020.12.07.12.49.29","modelCode":"GTRR35L","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"13977.5"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"86095"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"83865"}},"gt-r-my20":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"68170.83"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.08","modelCode":"GTRR35L","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"13634.17"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"84035"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"81805"}},"navara-my19":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"22350"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.11","modelCode":"NAVARAD23B","OTR":{"modelPrice":"22670"}},"juke-my19":{"Updated_On":"2020.12.01.10.05.50","modelCode":"JUKEF16A","OTR":{"modelPrice":"18360"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"18090"}},"test-CC-hidden-price":{"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.10","modelCode":"XTRAILT32D","OTR":{"modelPrice":"26835"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"25910"}},"new-qashqai-cs":{"Retail":{"modelPrice":"16475"},"Updated_On":"2020.10.01.17.48.09","modelCode":"QASHQAIJ11B","VAT Only":{"modelPrice":"3295"},"OTR":{"modelPrice":"19995"},"Retail with VAT":{"modelPrice":"19770"}}}
COOKIES
This Cookie Policy is intended to inform you how Nissan uses a technology called “cookies” and web server logs, to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site.
WHAT ARE COOKIES?
Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile phone browser by websites that you visit. Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or to improve the user experience, as well as to provide certain information to the owners of the website. Our cookies may include information about your online preferences and allow us to tailor our websites to your interests, and often include an anonymous unique identifier.
For further details on cookies, please visit https://ico.org.uk/ where you can find comprehensive information on cookies and similar technologies.
CONSENT TO USE OF COOKIES ON THIS WEBSITE
By continuing to use our site, you are deemed to consent to our use of the cookies described in this policy.   If you do not consent to our use of cookies, then please read the next section “Amending your cookie preferences”.
Amending your cookie preferences
You can amend your cookie preferences at any time using the button below.   By opting out of certain cookies some personalised services will not be provided to you. If you choose to block all cookies, some aspects of the site may not work properly and you may not be able to access all or part of the site.  You may not reject the use of ‘strictly necessary  ’ cookies as these are vital to run the website and store your previous cookie preferences.
Amend cookie preferences
Amend cookie preferences
Amend cookie preferences
HOW DO WE USE COOKIES?
Information supplied by cookies can help us to analyse your use of our websites and help us to provide you with a better online user experience tailored to your interests. The information our cookies collect is not used to identify who you are, or to send you advertising by e-mail or post. Further, we do not use cookies to provide targeted and personalised advertising to children.
WHAT TYPE OF COOKIES DO WE USE FOR WHAT PURPOSES?
Functional
Vendor
Privacy Policy
Description
Purpose
Nissan
Nissan Privacy Policy
Nissan functional cookies allow for enhanced user experience through the storing of previous preferences, delivering a tailored onsite experience.
These cookies enable the website to provide enhanced functionality and personalisation. They may be set by us or by third party providers whose services we have added to our pages. If you do not allow these cookies then some or all of these services may not function properly.
Targeting
Vendor
Privacy Policy
Description
Purpose
DV360
DV360 Privacy Policy
This partner allows us to optimise our programmatic display advertising campaigns, build lookalike audiences, and retarget users who have been on site.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Nissan
Nissan Privacy Policy
Nissan targeting cookies allow for enhanced user experience through the storing of previous preferences, delivering a tailored onsite experience.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Oracle
Oracle Privacy Policy
The following Oracle features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Oracle cookies, having the following functionalities:
Tags placed on the website Marketing insights and other analytics
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Sophus
Sophus Privacy Policy
Sophus tags allow for the collection and analysis of onsite data
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Ignition One
Ignition One Privacy Policy
Ignition one tags track user behaviour across the site and amylase when is best to present a user with a tailored message.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Astute Metrics
Astute Metric Privacy Policy
The purpose of the tag is to enable you to attribute conversion (to a telephone contact) by dealer for any tracked digital activity, allowing effective evaluation of media, or campaign activities.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Adobe
Adobe Privacy Policy
Adobe Experience Cloud ID allow advertisers to track visitors across different domains and enable data sharing among different Experience Cloud solutions.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Teads
Teads Privacy Policy
Teads tags collects and uses data to help make online advertising more relevant as well as for ad delivery and reporting purposes.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Verizon
Verizon Privacy Policy
This partner allows us to optimise our programmatic display advertising campaigns, build lookalike audiences, and retarget users who have been on site.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Xandr
Xandr Privacy Policy
This partner allows us to optimise our programmatic display advertising campaigns, build lookalike audiences, and retarget users who have been on site
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Pardot
Pardot Privacy Policy
Pardot aids in B2B marketing optimisations for Fleet on Nissan.co.uk.
These cookies may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Some of these cookies may be based on your geolocation and may be used by Nissan or our advertising partners to understand your interests and show you relevant adverts on other sites. Furthermore, we may use this information to send you personalised advertisements that would better match your expectations, subject to your prior express consent.
Strictly Necessary
Vendor
Privacy Policy
Description
Purpose
Nissan
Nissan Privacy Policy
Nissan strictly necessary cookies allow for enhanced user experience through the storing of previous preferences, delivering a tailored onsite experience.
These cookies are necessary for the website to function and cannot be switched off in our systems. They are usually only set in response to actions made by you which amount to a request for services, such as setting your privacy preferences, logging in or filling in forms. You can set your browser to block or alert you about these cookies, but some parts of the site will not then work. These cookies do not store any personal data.
Social Media
Vendor
Privacy Policy
Description
Purpose
Facebook
Facebook Cookie Policy Facebook Privacy Policy
The following Facebook features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Facebook cookies:
• Like button (enables user to Like the item on Facebook) • Facebook Share (enables the user to share the item on Facebook) • Facebook Social Graph (enables our websites to pull elements of Facebook into our websites, such as user profile images, public Facebook posts
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
Twitter
Twitter Privacy Policy
The following Twitter features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Twitter cookies:
• Twitter log-in (enables the user to log into their Twitter account and interact with our websites through that account) • Twitter share, Data Aggregator/Supplier, Mobile, Social Media
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
Flickr
Flickr Privacy Policy
The following Flickr features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Flickr cookies:
• Flickr Log-In (enables the user to log into their Flickr account and interact with our websites through that account)
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
Instagram
Instagram Privacy Policy
The following Instagram features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Instagram cookies:
• Instagram Log-In (enables the user to log into their Instagram account and interact with our websites through that account)
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
Pinterest
Pinterest Privacy Policy
The following Pinterest features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Pinterest cookies:
• Pin-It Button (enables the user to pin the item on their Pinterest page)
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
YouTube
Youtube Privacy Policy
The following YouTube features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place YouTube cookies:
• YouTube video player (enables the viewing of YouTube videos on our websites) • YouTube account log-in (enables the user to log into their YouTube account and interact with the DEC through that account)
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
Google Inc.
Google Inc. Privacy Policy
The following YouTube features may be integrated into our websites and may read or place Google cookies:
• Google+1 button (enables the user to tag the item on their Google+ account) • Google log-in (enables the user to log into their Google account and interact with our website through that account) • Google Ads Remarketing • Google Ads Conversion Tracking • Google Analytics: Universal Analytics • Google Tag Manager • Google Marketing • Floodlight Counter • Conversion Linker • Custom Image • Ad Network • Ad Server • Analytics Provider • Publisher • Mobile
These cookies are set by a range of social media services that we have added to our website to enable you to share our content with your friends and networks. They are capable of tracking your browser across other sites and building up a profile of your interests. This may impact the content and messages you see on other websites you visit.
Performance
Vendor
Privacy Policy
Description
Purpose
Decibel
Decibel Privacy Policy
Decibel Insight is a user behaviour tracking tool that allows businesses to view how users interact with their platform(s).  Decibel is able to identify changes of behavior through tailored funnels and segments and through sessions replays. Decibel also collects data regarding clickthrough rates and provides a generic and localised view of heatmaps to analyse what are the most engaging elements/topics for customers.
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.
OnCrawl
OnCrawl Privacy Policy
OnCrawl is a semantic web crawler for state of the art Enterprise SEO Audits. Functions include discoverin errors in HTML and link structure and content that can impact rankings in search engines.
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.
Majestic SEO
Majestic SEO Privacy Policy
The Majestic SEO tool allows understanding of the third party sites backlinking to Nissan.co.uk.
These cookies allow us to count visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site. They help us to know which pages are the most and least popular and see how visitors move around the site. All information these cookies collect is aggregated and therefore anonymous.
Home
Cookies
